bullying in the chat bullying in the
bullying en el chat bullying en el
chat another melon but no no no no another
chat otro melón pero no no no no otro
melon no family let's see the reaction
melón no familia vamos a ver la reacción
that Terelu has had the striking
que ha tenido terelu la llamativa
reaction that Terelu Campos has had to
reacción que ha tenido terelu Campos a
the
la
accusation of her What's his name with
imputación de su Cómo se llama con
father-in-law no I mean Carl's father
suegro no O sea el padre de Carl
Constancia is his
constancia es su
father-in-law with whom he has to sit at
consuegro con el que se tiene que sentar
the wedding table
la mesa de boda
no
no
[ __ ] what a
ostia qué
ballot what a ballot what Uy Oy well
papeleta qué papeleta qué Uy Oy bueno
those of you who are watching this in the
los que estáis viendo esto en el
extract uploaded to Youtube remind you
extracto subido a Youtube recordaros a
all that I would love to know your
todos que me encantaría conocer vuestra
opinion in the comments box but
opinión en la caja de comentarios pero
please with respect okay Give your
por favor con respeto vale Dad vuestra
opinion I want to know what you think on
opinión Quiero saber qué pensáis sobre
this subject but all with respect and
este tema pero todos con respeto y
leave me a Like if you like this
dejarme un Like si os gusta este
content so that the video is positioned what a
contenido para que el vídeo se posicione
ballot of let's see you're going to me you're
vaya papeleta de a ver me vais a me va
going to mess with elu you're not going to
os vais a meter con elu no os vais a
mess with Terelu too right well I feel
meter con terelu también verdad pues yo
very sorry for Terelu
a mí me da mucha lástima terelu
eh I don't like Terelu at all says Roxy Hey
eh No me gusta nada terelu dice Roxy Oye
but Hey but it gives us also you're going to
pero Oye pero nos da también os vais a
mess with  terelu I mean Hey but
meter con terelu o sea Oye pero no
we're not seeing eye to eye on anything today No, the
estamos coincidiendo en nada hoy no el
father and the Dalton brothers Hey but you don't
padre y los hermanos Dalton Oye pero
have much of a crush on you guys Would you
tenéis poco cachón de ustedes a ustedes
like to You would like to of course since you dislike her Since you
os gustaría a ustedes os gustaría claro
dislike her well
es que ya como os cae mal como os cae
not empathize with her Of course
mal pues no empatizar con ella Claro
but you guys would
pero a ustedes os
like to raise a girl Between
gustaría criar una niña Entre
cottons 25 27 years old I don't know how old
algodones 25 27 años no sé cuánto tiene
Alejandra is but maybe and she comes to you
Alejandra pero por ahí y que os venga
with this man who has gone through the
con este hombre que se ha repasado el
entire penal code from p aá in alphabetical order
código penal entero de p aá en orden
man well the truth is that it's a
hombre pues la verdad que es un
disappointment the truth is that it's a disappointment
disgusto la verdad que es un disgusto
no I mean with mother-in-law
no O sea con suegra
Mar Flores of course there isn't like there
mar flores claro ahí tampoco como que
was the best vibe not to say no I don't
hubiese el mejor rollo no digamos
know all the details very well
no no conozco muy bien todos los
but there isn't like there was
detalles pero ahí no es como que hubiese
the best vibe either but of course
el mejor rollo tampoco pero claro ya que
the father-in-law [ __ ] the father-in-law
el consuegro el consuegro se las
brings it eh
trae eh
the father-in-law has his thing
el consuegro tiene tiene su miga
eh And of course if you say Well because it
eh Y claro si tú dices Bueno porque
can happen many times in some
puede pasar muchas veces en algunas
families in the best families this happens
familias en las mejores familias pasa
eh this happens in the best
eh esto pasa en las mejores
families Greetings Javi  I hope to see you
familias Saludos Javi Ojalá ver algún
around here one day, man Alexandra, but you
día por aquí hombre Alexandra pero te
've come on too high, do you think that ik
has venido muy arriba tú crees que ik
could come, man? I think we would do it
podría venir hombre Yo creo que lo
on the main floor, I'm telling you,
haríamos en el principal también te digo
eh, if he came one day around here we would
eh si viniese que era un día por aquí lo
do it on the main floor, but man, I don't
haríamos en el principal pero hombre no
know, eh, I don't know, we'll see, we'll see, we'll
sé yo eh No sé yo ya veremos ya veremos
see what the future holds for us, who was
ya veremos el futuro lo que nos depara
going to tell us that we
quién nos iba a decir a nosotros que
were going to be here with 1,615
íbamos a estar aquí con 1615
wonderful
maravillosos
members, who was going to
miembros quién nos lo iba a
tell us the striking reaction of Terelu
decir la llamativa reacción de terelu
Campos to the accusation of Carlos's father,
Campos a la imputación del padre de
constancia, what I was going to
Carlos constancia que lo que os iba a
tell you, no, it's always a black sheep,
decir no tú siempre es un garbanzo negro
maybe a black sheep, whatever you
pued ha un garbanzo negro lo que tú
want, but of course, it's not that there's a
quieras pero claro aquí no es que haya
black sheep, here it's the
un garbanzo negro aquí es que el
son, let's see, being honest, not with
hijo o sea a ver siendo sinceros no con
luck in the family, with luck in the
suerte en la familia con suerte en la
family there's a sheep that isn't
familia hay un garbanzo que no esté
black because of course the son, the son has
negro porque claro el hijo el hijo tiene
a few,
unas cuantas
not the son-in-law, Terelu's son-in-law has
no el yerno el yerno de terelu tiene
a few things here, not the son-in-law.
unas cuantas de cosillas por ahí no el
Brothers of the son-in-law
yerno Los Hermanos del yerno
and his daughter I also dislike him I don't
y su niña también me cae mal no me
remember his name come on Carmenchu
acuerdo de cómo se llama venga carmenchu
come on more hate For God's sake how you take
venga más odio Por Dios cómo tomáis las
things I empathize with Terelu I give her my
cosas yo empatizo con terelu le doy mi
hand I would not like at all to be in her
mano no me gustaría nada estar en su
place do not
lugar no me lo
deny it to me Carl's father Constancia the
neguis el padre de Carl constancia la
Rubio couple so that he
pareja Rubio para que se
[Music]
[Música]
finds out Oh my chat has gone away I have gone away
entere Ay se me ha ido el chat se me ha
who is that lady who
ido el chat quién es esa señora que ha
said that she doesn't like Alejandra and that she couldn't
dicho que le cae mal Alejandra y que no
remember her
se acordaba de su
name is on everyone's lips Carlos
nombre está en Boca de todos Carlos
Constancia di Costigliole could
constancia di costigliole podría estar
allegedly be involved in the case for
supuestamente implicado en el caso por
which his sons Roco and
el que se investiga a sus hijos roco y
Pietro are being investigated after alleged attempted
Pietro tras presunto intento de
murder my goodness my goodness my goodness
asesinato madre mía madre mía madre
my goodness has been included in the list of
mía ha sido incluido en la lista de
people investigated by the
personas investigadas por la fiscalía de
Turin prosecutor's office in the case of his children for
turín en la causa de sus hijos por
alleged document forgery since it is
supuesta falsificación documental ya que
suspected that he would have allegedly
se sospecha que supuestamente habría
altered and modified a document
Alterado y modificado un documento
illegally to make it easier for a
ilegalmente para facilitar que una
third person to introduce
persona una tercera persona introdujera
a telephone into
un teléfono en
prison so that they could
prisión de manera que se pudieran
communicate with each other and with people
comunicar entre sí y con personas del
outside
exterior
ugh what an element Look look look at
puf menudo elemento Mira mira mira la
mit terelu's face Look look look at
cara de mit terelu Mira
mit terelu's face Lili
mira mira la cara de mit terelu Lili
for the thumbnail Look at her
para la miniatura
And you don't empathize with this
Mírala Y ustedes no empatizar con esta
lady
señora
And you're telling me not to
Y ustedes me estáis diciendo que no
empathize with this Poor
empatizar con esta Pobre
woman Javi repeats the last name Fernández I
mujer Javi repite el apellido Fernández
think her name was
creo que se llamaba
carmenchu
carmenchu
Chela you don't empathize with this
Chela ustedes no empatizar con esta
woman are you
mujer de
really going to tell me that you're
verdad me vais a decir que estáis en
against this Poor man look at the
contra de esta Pobre hombre mira el
soul What do you mean, well no Pilar Hey I
alma Cómo que pues no Pilar Oye a mí me
like the good people here and what
gusta aquí la buena gente y lo que no
can't be is that there are 1600 people in the
puede ser que haya 1600 personas en el
live show and 700 likes that's not very
directo y y 700 likes eso no es muy de
good people good people give the like
buena gente la buena gente le da al like
that's
que es
free the crime is a little bad
gratuito el delito está un poco chungo
already but let's see when it's your normality and
ya pero a ver cuando es tu normalidad y
it's what you
es en lo que te
handle you
manejas
know when it's in the environment in which you
sabes cuando es en el ambiente en el que
handle yourself and in the terms in which
te manejas y en los términos en los que
you move
te mueves
u terelu terelu terelu terelu
u terelu terelu terelu terelu está está
things are bad eh terelu I mean terelu is going through a
chunga la cosa eh terelu o sea terelu lo
bad time eh  I
está pasando lo está pasando mal eh o
mean, you guys are all [ __ ],
sea yo es que ustedes sois unos cabrones
eh, I give my hand to
eh yo le doy mi mano a
Terelu, I'm against my entire chat
terelu estoy en contra de todo mi chat
today you are bad people.
hoy sois mala gente
How come you are not in favor of having him
Cómo es que no estáis a favor de tenerlo
in this controversy, wow, the girl, the
en esta polémica vaya la niña el
upset that the mother is having
disgusto que le está dando a la madre
with the boyfriends that the mother brings home
con los novios que le trae a casa la
thinking that the girl was going to be
madre pensando que la niña iba a estar
with who, with who, with
con con quién con
who, did the mother think the girl
quién con quién se creía la madre que
could be with?
podía estar la niña
Javi congratulates the Mediaset makeup artists.
Javi felicita a los maquilladores de
Hey, but let's see, I'll tell you one thing, he
mediaset Oye pero a ver te digo una cosa
's
que está
scared. But I'll tell you one thing, she's
asustado Pero te digo una cosa que está
scared.
asustada
Damn, he was going to get her out of poverty. Let's see,
Que la iba a sacar de pobre A ver
not get her out of poverty, but yes, I think she was, she was
no sacarla de pobre pero sí que yo creo
a girl who was very
que era era una niña que estaba muy
among arg godones and what was least
entre arg godones y lo que menos se
expected and besides, we're talking about
esperaba y aparte estamos hablando de
a classist person because Terel is a
una persona clasista porque terel es una
classist person, right? So in the end, I
persona clasista no Entonces al final yo
think that she,
creo que ella
HM, the only thing she can get out of Carlos,
HM lo único que puede sacar de Carlos
constancy, is that look, he's the son of
constancia Es que mira que es el hijo de
another very famous person, but Ugh, with
de otra persona muy famosa pero Uf con
all the famous people there, go ahead and take the
todos los famosos que hay váy atel a la
girl, eh. And besides, she's not anymore  that he is the
chavala eh Y aparte ya no es que sea un
girl's boyfriend, of course he will
novio de la niña claro es que va a ser
always be the father of her grandson,
siempre el padre de su nieto
buah that's nothing eh
buah ahí es nada eh
there at all
ahí en nada
eh because he had falsified a document
eh porque había falsificado un documento
so that an ex-girlfriend of an ex-girlfriend of
para que una exnovia de una exnovia de
Pietro would go to jail to see him and
Pietro fuera a la cárcel a verle y
give him a
pasarle un
phone number, I don't
teléfono no
have You think that's any idea of ​​what you
tengo Tú crees que es idea de lo que me
're talking about,
estás hablando de
really speaking as if you were asking me
verdad hablando como si me preguntaras
in Japanese Well maybe you think it can
en japonés Pues igual tú crees que puede
affect the relationship, I don't know what you
afectar a la relación no sé de qu me
're talking about okay I can tell you
estás hablando vale puedo contar
that it's that it's that I don't know what it is nothing
que es que es que no sé qué es nada
good because this half c no this
bueno pues porque esto media c no esto
is half c no this is the pharmacy that
es media c no est es la farmacia que
is there on the
está ahí en la
corner yes yes this is the
esquina sí sí esto es la zona de los
bar area of ​​the but let's
bares de la pero a
see
ver
mm is that in
mm es que en
reality in reality ter what is she going to
realidad en realidad ter que te va a
answer you regarding this no that
contestar respecto a esto no
family is a little girl Yes, but
esa familia es una jollita Sí ya pero
of course they ask Terelu on the street
claro le preguntan a terelu por la calle
that I understand that the boy is
que yo entiendo que que el muchacho está
doing his job but in reality what is
haciendo su trabajo pero en realidad qué
Terelu going to tell you regarding that, no, on
te va a decir terelu respecto a eso no a
that subject, no now the face, the face is not
ese tema no ahora la cara la cara no es
good
buena
eh the face is the mirror of the soul eh
eh la la cara es el espejo del alma eh
the face is the mirror of the soul and we have to
la cara es el espejo del alma y tenemos
recognize that the reaction is not that it is
que reconocer que la reacción no que
scary that it is scary
está asusta que está asusta
my goodness
madre mía
eh my goodness
eh madre mía
eh if you don't pay for it you don't answer but
eh si no la pagas no contestas pero
well in the end those jobs I don't
bueno al final esos trabajo yo eso no lo
see anything wrong with that but it is true that what is she
veo mal pero sí que es verdad que qué te
going to say to you, I mean if they catch you on the
va a decir o sea si te cogen por la
street and that neither you know
calle y que tampoco vete tú a saber que
how informed she is,
tan informada está
you know what people say out there
no vete tú a saber dice por ahí la gente
the face is her normal face as always no no no
la cara es su cara normal de siempre no
no man in this video you see her
no no no hombre en este vídeo se la ve
ailla in that video she looked austed
ailla en ese vídeo se la veía austad
illa
illa